<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">JATransit</string>
    <string name="title_activity">JA Transit</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Details</string>
    <string name= "action_search">Search</string>
    <string name="action_location_found">Location Found</string>
    <string name="action_refresh">Refresh</string>
    <string name="action_contacts">Contacts</string>
    <string name="action_help">Help</string>
    <string name="action_check_updates">Check for Updates</string>

    <string name="nearby">NEARBY</string>
    <!-- Search  -->
    <string name="search_hint">Route#.. Ori</string>

    <string name="body">This android application displays nearby bus timing information and bus routes that JUTC operates.
                        This application utilizes the GPS built in to your smart phone to pinpoint your
                        location. The application will then tie you to the nearest bus stop and display a list of the buses arriving
                        at that bus stop in the order of arrival time.
    </string>
    <string-array name="questions">
        <item>1. What does the Acronym JUTC mean?</item>
        <item>2. What is the JUTC SMART CARD?</item>
        <item>3. What is the size and “make up” of the JUTC fleet?</item>
        <item>4. Who designed the JATransit Application? </item>
        <item>5. How much does the JATransit Application cost?  </item>
        <item>6. Where does the JATransit Application work?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="answers">
        <item>Jamaica Urban Transit Company</item>
        <item>This is a “cashless system” of bus fare payment, which JUTC commuters can use
              for travel within the Kingston Metropolitan Transportation Region (KMTR). The
              card is reusable and rechargeable and should not be thrown away – similar to a credit card.</item>
        <item>The fleet size is now approximately 460 buses and including the artic, bi-artic, buses for
            the handicapped and luxury coaches. The most common make in the fleet is Volvo.</item>
        <item>The JATransit app was designed by 5 Students from the Department of Computing at the UWI,
            Mona. Namely: Anthony Scott, Caliph Cole, Percival Reid, Antoinette Todd and Hertbert McNeil</item>
        <item>The JATransit application is completely free to everyone with an Android Smartphone.</item>
        <item>The JATransit application is intended to work in the areas of Jamaica served by scheduled JUTC bus service.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="icon">
        <item>Nearby Icon</item>
        <item>Route Icon</item>
        <item>Trip Icon</item>
        <item>Map</item>
        <item>Search</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="details">
        <item> Click to see all the buses near you based on your current location.
List items are clickable.
</item>
        <item>Click here to see all the routes and can search bus routes based on
            route number, origin or destination. List items are clickable, click to view static timetable
Static Time Table - Pinch out to zoom out to see the timetable for your route</item>
        <item> Click here to get all the bus routes for your trip based on the origin and destination.</item>
        <item>Click here to see all the buses around you  based on your current location.</item>
        <item>Click here to complete a quick search of a route.</item>


    </string-array>
</resources>
